Guide to the Elizabeth Page Harris Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family Papers, 1808-1978; Series II; 12.5' (28 boxes)
  - Manchester, Vermont
    - House notes, undated (Box 43, Folder 942)
    - House plans, 1944, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 943)
    - House rental, 1944-1967, undated (Box 43, Folder 944)
    - House rental receipts, 1955-1958 (Box 43, Folder 945)
    - House repairs, 1961, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 946-947)
    - Manchester Village Association, Inc., 1963-1969 (Box 43, Folder 948-949)
    - Manchester Welfare and Nursing Association, 1949-1963 (Box 43, Folder 950)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1968, undated (Box 43, Folder 951-952)
    - Papers, undated (Box 43, Folder 953)
    - The Southern Vermont Art Center, 1951-1966, undated (Box 43, Folder 954)
    - Telephone directory: Bennington district, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 955)
    - Village of Manchester: zoning ordinance, undated (Box 43, Folder 956)
  - Maps, undated (Box 43, Folder 957)
  - Medicare and Blue Cross, 1967-1968, undated (Box 43, Folder 958)
    - Blue Cross, 1949-1968 (Box 43, Folder 959)
    - Continental Causality Co. Golden 65, 1960-1968 (Box 44, Folder 960)
  - Memberships, 1921-1969, undated (Box 44, Folder 961)
  - Memorabilia
    - Beads, undated (Box 44, Folder 962)
    - Copper disc, undated (Box 44, Folder 963)
    - Crochet work, undated (Box 44, Folder 964)
    - Handkerchief, undated (Box 44, Folder 965)
    - Handkerchief, red, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 966)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 44, Folder 967)
  - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 44, Folder 968)
  - The Mohonk Lodge, 1939-1949, undated (Box 44, Folder 969)
  - Notes, 1962-1967, undated (Box 44, Folder 970-971)
  - Notes and lists, 1961, undated (Box 44, Folder 972)
  - Notes in French, undated (Box 44, Folder 973)
  - Notes, miscellaneous, 1948-1969, undated (Box 44, Folder 974-976)
  - Notes on Bible study, 1909 (Box 44, Folder 977)
  - Notes on sewing, undated (Box 44, Folder 978)
  - Notes on various subjects, 1928, undated (Box 44, Folder 979)
  - Page family: commomplace book, undated (Box 45, Folder 980)
  - Page, Alfred Rider, 1932-1934 (Box 45, Folder 981)
  - Page, Angeline Rider: reminiscences, 1893, undated (Box 45, Folder 982)
  - Page, Elizabeth Merwin
    - Estate, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 983)
    - Income taxes, 1939 (Box 45, Folder 984)
  - Passports, 1920, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 985-986)
  - Plan of readjustment, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 987)
  - Poetry, 1908-1947, undated (Box 45, Folder 988-989)
  - Prescriptions, 1912-1966, undated (Box 45, Folder 990)
  - Printed materials
    - ADA World, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 991)
    - Albert Memorial Tower, undated (Box 45, Folder 992)
    - Annual report of Writers' War Board, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 993)
    - Brown, John Franklin. "Textbooks and Publishers", undated (Box 45, Folder 994)
    - Calendars, 1916-1927 (Box 45, Folder 995)
    - Catalogues, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 996-997)
    - Catechism for Young Children, 1840 (Box 45, Folder 998)
    - Christmas, undated (Box 45, Folder 999)
    - Church programs, 1922, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 1000)
    - College-Entrance Requirements in English, Circa 1913 (Box 45, Folder 1001)
    - Doubleday One Dollar Book Club, undated (Box 45, Folder 1002)
    - "Giosue Carducci", undated (Box 45, Folder 1003)
    - Guayule, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 1004)
    - Income taxes, 1942, undated (Box 45, Folder 1005)
    - Lake Mohonk Mountain House, 1939, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 1006)
    - Library brochures, undated (Box 45, Folder 1007)
    - Medical subjects, undated (Box 45, Folder 1008)
    - Military Training for School Boys, undated (Box 45, Folder 1009)
    - Miscellaneous, 1898-1965, undated (Box 46, Folder 1010-1015)
    - La Mujee Christiana, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 1016)
    - New books list, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1017)
    - Newspapers clippings
      - Great Britain and the royal family, 1946-1960, undated (Box 46, Folder 1018)
      - Historical interest, 1924-1925, undated (Box 46, Folder 1019)
      - Miscellaneous, 1916-1960, undated (Box 46, Folder 1020-1021)
      - New York, 1917-1943, undated (Box 46, Folder 1022)
      - People, 1916-1961, undated (Box 46, Folder 1023)
      - Politics, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 1024)
      - Vermont, 1931, 1935, undated (Box 46, Folder 1025)
    - Orthodietics chart, undated (Box 46, Folder 1026)
    - Padua Hills News Notes, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 1027)
    - Parks and Plateaus, undated (Box 46, Folder 1028)
    - The Schauffler Quarterly, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 1029)
    - "A Service of Intercession for the Peace of the World", 1914 (Box 46, Folder 1030)
    - The Urantis Book, undated (Box 46, Folder 1031)
    - "Where Jobs Come From", undated (Box 46, Folder 1032)
    - Wildflower namer, undated (Box 46, Folder 1033)
    - Wyoming, 1950-1968, undated (Box 46, Folder 1034)
  - Professional files
    - Complimentary copies, 1932, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1035)
    - Contracts, 1929-1964 (Box 46, Folder 1036)
    - Copyright renewal, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 1037)
    - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc., 1938-1955 (Box 46, Folder 1038)
    - Guidelines for authors, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 1039)
    - Instructions for writers, 1938-1940, undated (Box 46, Folder 1040)
    - Organizations
      - The Authors League of America, Inc., 1940-1948 (Box 46, Folder 1041)
      - The Authors League of America, Inc., 1942-1952, undated (Box 47, Folder 1042-1043)
      - California Writers Guild, 1938, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 1044)
      - League of American Writers, Inc., 1939-1941, undated (Box 47, Folder 1045)
      - League of Vermont Writers, 1942-1952 (Box 47, Folder 1046)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946.1955, undated (Box 47, Folder 1047)
    - Papers, 1941-1965 (Box 47, Folder 1048)
    - Rejection slips, 1933-1934, undated (Box 47, Folder 1049)
    - Royalty statements, 1930-1967 (Box 47, Folder 1050-1052)
    - Speaking notes, 1940-1964, undated (Box 47, Folder 1053-1054)
  - Recipes, undated (Box 47, Folder 1055)
  - Rider, Richard Price, 1920 (Box 47, Folder 1056)
  - Robertson family, 1808-1895 (Box 47, Folder 1057)
  - Roe family, 1948-1960, undated (Box 47, Folder 1058)
  - Roe, Caroline Marsh
    - "A Daytime Incident", undated (Box 47, Folder 1059)
    - "A Fairy Story", undated (Box 47, Folder 1060)
    - "How the Panama Was Saved", undated (Box 47, Folder 1061)
  - Safe deposit box, 1943-1965, undated (Box 47, Folder 1062)
  - Schauffler, Marjorie Page, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 1063)
  - Scrapbooks, 1894, undated (Box 47, Folder 1064-1065)
  - Sound recordings, undated (Box 48, Folder 1066)
  - Stenographer's notebooks, 1968, undated (Box 48, Folder 1067-1068)
  - "A Story", Circa 1923 (Box 48, Folder 1069)
  - Sunday school notes, undated (Box 48, Folder 1070)
  - Tallant, Edith, undated (Box 48, Folder 1071)
  - Theater programs, 1915-1962, undated (Box 48, Folder 1072)
  - Thoughts on pacificism, undated (Box 48, Folder 1073)
  - Tompkins, Stuart Ramsay, 1953-1958, undated (Box 48, Folder 1074)
  - Travel information
    - Air travel, 1960, undated (Box 48, Folder 1075)
    - Bahama Islands, undated (Box 48, Folder 1076)
    - California, 1940, undated (Box 48, Folder 1077)
    - Colorado, undated (Box 48, Folder 1078)
    - Europe, 1948-1967, undated (Box 48, Folder 1079)
    - Florida, undated (Box 48, Folder 1080)
    - Massachusetts, undated (Box 48, Folder 1081)
    - Mexico, 1951-1964, undated (Box 48, Folder 1082-1083)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 48, Folder 1084)
    - New York (City), undated (Box 48, Folder 1085)
    - New York (State), 1940, undated (Box 48, Folder 1086)
    - Ocean voyages, 1954-1958, undated (Box 48, Folder 1087-1089)
    - Pennsylvania, undated (Box 48, Folder 1090)
    - Railroad timetables, 1919-1925 (Box 49, Folder 1091)
    - Road maps, 1942-1962, undated (Box 49, Folder 1092)
    - Street map of Brooklyn, N.Y., undated (Box 49, Folder 1093)
    - United States, general, undated (Box 49, Folder 1094)
    - Vermont, undated (Box 49, Folder 1095)
    - Virgin Islands, undated (Box 49, Folder 1096)
    - Virginia, 1935, undated (Box 49, Folder 1097)
    - Western United States, 1954, undated (Box 49, Folder 1098)
    - Wyoming, undated (Box 49, Folder 1099)
  - Travels
    - California, undated (Box 49, Folder 1100)
    - Canary Islands, 1961-1968 (Box 49, Folder 1101)
    - Jamaica, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 1102)
    - Mexico, 1967-1968 (Box 49, Folder 1103)
    - "Round-the-world", 1962 (Box 49, Folder 1104-1105)
    - Scandanavia and Great Britain, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1106-1108)
  - 2201 Loring Place, undated (Box 50, Folder 1109)
  - University Heights Presbyterian Church, 1925, undated (Box 50, Folder 1110)
    - Anniversary booklet, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 1111)
  - Vannier, Marion. L., 1942, 1966, undated (Box 50, Folder 1112)
  - Vassar College
    - Catalogues, 1883, 1908 (Box 50, Folder 1113-1114)
    - Centennial, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1115-1116)
    - Class of 1912, 1908-1967 (Box 50, Folder 1117)
      - Bulletins, 1913-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1118-1122)
      - Fiftieth reunion, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 1123)
      - Newsletters, 1939-1967 (Box 50, Folder 1124)
      - Report of twenty-fifth reunion, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 1125)
      - Twenty-fifth reunion, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 1126)
    - "Classroom '64", 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1127)
    - Miscellaneous, 1908-1967, undated (Box 51, Folder 1128)
    - Miscellaneous printed, 1927-1964, undated (Box 51, Folder 1129-1130)
    - School work
      - Bibliographies, 1912 (Box 51, Folder 1131)
      - English paper on the conversion of Newman, 1912 (Box 51, Folder 1132)
      - Notes on American history, 1911-1912 (Box 51, Folder 1133)
      - Notes on economics, 1910 (Box 51, Folder 1134)
      - Notes on "King Lear", 1910 (Box 51, Folder 1135)
      - Notes on physics, 1911 (Box 51, Folder 1136)
      - Notes on psychology, undated (Box 51, Folder 1137)
      - Notes on Russian history, undated (Box 51, Folder 1138)
      - Notes on social history, undated (Box 51, Folder 1139)
      - Spanish exercises and notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 1140)
    - Scrapbook, 1908-1914 (Box 52, Folder 1141)
    - Vassar Alumnae Magazine, 1943-1967 (Box 53, Folder 1142-1143)
    - Vassar Alumnae News Letter, 1960-1967 (Box 53, Folder 1144)
    - Vassar College Bulletin, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 1145)
    - Vassar Quarterly, 1932 May (Box 53, Folder 1146)
    - Vassar-Yale merger, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 1147)
    - Vermont Vassar Club, 1954-1968, undated (Box 53, Folder 1148)
  - Vermont
    - Notes on farmers cooperatives, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 1149)
    - Printed works, 1926-1965, undated (Box 53, Folder 1150)
  - Vermont Guild of Oldtime Crafts & Industries, 1942, undated (Box 53, Folder 1151)
  - Walnut Hill School
    - English history exams, 1915 (Box 53, Folder 1152)
    - Grade book, 1914 (Box 53, Folder 1153)
    - Students' Hand-Book, 1915 (Box 53, Folder 1154)
    - Writings: "A Session of Pluto's Court", undated (Box 53, Folder 1155)
    - Writings: "Walnut Hill Winnie; or, Traced by a Laundry Mark", undated (Box 53, Folder 1156)
  - Watercolors, 1927, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 1157-1158)
  - Wickham family, 1942, undated (Box 53, Folder 1159)
  - Willits, Nathalie, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 1160)
  - Women's Auxiliary of the New York University YMCA, 1922-1926 (Box 53, Folder 1161)
  - World War I
    - Address book, 1919 (Box 53, Folder 1162)
    - American Expeditionary Force: printed works, 1919, undated (Box 53, Folder 1163)
    - American Red Cross, 1916, 1919, undated (Box 54, Folder 1164-1165)
      - Handbook of Information and Instructions for Home Service Sections, 1918 (Box 54, Folder 1166)
      - Lecture notes, 1919 (Box 54, Folder 1167)
      - Note cards on disabled veterans, 1919-1920 (Box 54, Folder 1168-1169)
      - Notebook, Circa 1919 (Box 54, Folder 1170)
      - Photograph, undated (Box 54, Folder 1171)
      - Printed materials, 1918, 1920 (Box 54, Folder 1172)
    - Camp Merritt, New Jersey, undated (Box 54, Folder 1173)
    - Diary, 1919 (Box 54, Folder 1174)
    - France: guidebooks, 1918, undated (Box 54, Folder 1175)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1919, undated (Box 54, Folder 1176)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1917-1919, undated (Box 54, Folder 1177-1180)
    - Passport, identity card, travel permit, 1918-1919 (Box 54, Folder 1181)
    - Photographs, 1919, undated (Box 54, Folder 1182-1185)
    - Photographs: France, undated (Box 55, Folder 1186)
    - Photographs of friends, undated (Box 55, Folder 1187)
    - Postcards
      - Camp, undated (Box 55, Folder 1188-1189)
      - France, 1919, undated (Box 55, Folder 1190-1192)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 55, Folder 1193)
    - Snapshots, undated (Box 55, Folder 1194)
    - Poetry, undated (Box 55, Folder 1195-1196)
    - Printed works
      - The American Soldiers' Souvenir of Aix-les-Bains, undated (Box 55, Folder 1197)
      - Archer, William. The Pirate's Progress: A Short History of the U-Boat, 1918 (Box 55, Folder 1198)
      - Church, Samuel Harden. The American Verdict on the War, 1915 (Box 55, Folder 1199)
      - The Home Soldier, 1919 (Box 55, Folder 1200)
      - International Conciliation, 1918 (Box 55, Folder 1201)
      - Miscellaneous pamphlets, 1914-1919, undated (Box 55, Folder 1202-1203)
      - Miscellaneous pamphlets, 1917, 1919, undated (Box 56, Folder 1204)
      - The President's Flag Day Address, 1917 (Box 56, Folder 1205)
      - Report of the American Women's Hospitals, 1917 (Box 56, Folder 1206)
      - The Stars and Stripes, 1918-1919 (Box 56, Folder 1207-1208)
      - Van Vorst, B. France Our Ally, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 1209)
      - Woodward, Edwin C. War Impressions of an Engineer, undated (Box 56, Folder 1210)
    - Vassar College, 1918-1919 (Box 56, Folder 1211)
    - Walnut Hill School Newsletter, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 1212)
    - YMCA
      - Bills, receipts, notes, 1919, undated (Box 56, Folder 1213)
      - Cartoon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1214)
      - Insurance, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 1215)
      - Memorabilia, undated (Box 56, Folder 1216)
      - Memorial Day, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 1217)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 56, Folder 1218)
      - Notes, 1919, undated (Box 56, Folder 1219)
      - Pamphlets, 1918-1919, undated (Box 56, Folder 1220-1221)
      - Papers, 1918-1919, undated (Box 56, Folder 1222-1225)
      - Red Triangle League Bulletin, 1920 (Box 56, Folder 1226)
    - YWCA, 1917, undated (Box 56, Folder 1227)
  - World War II
    - Black-out instructions and newspaper clippings, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 1228)
    - Information on gas warfare, 1942, undated (Box 56, Folder 1229)
    - Papers, 1942-1943, undated (Box 56, Folder 1230)
    - Savings bonds, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 1231)
    - War rations, 1942-1946 (Box 56, Folder 1232)
- Grenfell Association, 1921-1969; Series III; 5.25' (14 boxes)
  Papers documenting the volunteer work of Elizabeth Page Harris with the International Grenfell Association are found in Series III, Boxes 57-70. Correspondence, arranged chronologically, comes first and it is followed by alphabetically arranged subject files. The series also includes a roll of ship model plans.
  - Correspondence, 1921-1924 March (Box 57, Folder 1233-1259)
  - Correspondence, 1924 April - 1925 March (Box 58, Folder 1260-1285)
  - Correspondence, 1925 April - 1926 August (Box 59, Folder 1286-1312)
  - Correspondence, 1926 September - 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1313-1338)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 60, Folder 1339)
  - Address on Sir Wilfred Grenfell, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 1340)
  - Bank statements, 1924-1925 (Box 60, Folder 1341)
  - Christmas card, undated (Box 60, Folder 1342)
  - Expenses, 1922 (Box 60, Folder 1343)
  - Health records
    - Brown's Cove, White Bay, Newfoundland, 1921 (Box 60, Folder 1344-1345)
    - Brown's Cove, White Bay, Newfoundland, undated (Box 61, Folder 1346)
  - Memorabilia
    See: Box 68, folder 1485
  - Miscellaneous, 1922-1941, undated (Box 61, Folder 1347)
  - New England. Grenfell Association, undated (Box 61, Folder 1348)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1922-1938, n.d (Box 61, Folder 1349)
  - Note cards
    See: Boxes 68-69, folder 1486-1487
  - Notebook, 1924-1925, undated (Box 61, Folder 1350)
  - Notebook and notes on ship models, 1923-1924, undated (Box 61, Folder 1351)
  - Notes and financial records, 1921-1925, undated (Box 61, Folder 1352)
  - Paintings, undated (Box 61, Folder 1353)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 61, Folder 1354)
    See also: Box 70, folder 1488
    - Newfoundland, undated (Box 61, Folder 1355)
    - Page, Elizabeth Merwin, undated (Box 61, Folder 1356)
    - Postcards
      - Cape Breton Island and Nova Scotia, undated (Box 61, Folder 1357)
      - Newfoundland, undated (Box 61, Folder 1358)
    - Snapshots, 1925-1926, undated (Box 61, Folder 1359-1362)
    - Slides, undated (Box 62, Folder 1363-1379)
    - Slides, undated (Box 63, Folder 1380-1396)
    - Slides, undated (Box 64, Folder 1397-1414)
    - Slides, undated (Box 65, Folder 1415-1427)
    - Glass negatives, undated (Box 65, Folder 1428-1437)
  - Printed works
    - Among the Deep Sea Fishers, 1921-1948 (Box 66, Folder 1438-1446)
    - Badger, Theodore L. Grenfell in Labrador, Circa 1928 (Box 66, Folder 1447)
    - Camp Fires and Camp Cookery, 1923 (Box 66, Folder 1448)
    - The Challenge of Labrador, undated (Box 66, Folder 1449)
    - Grenfell, Wilfred T. Labrador and North Newfoundland, 1924 (Box 66, Folder 1450)
    - Grenfell. Wilfred T. Quest and Conquest of Labrador, undated (Box 66, Folder 1451)
    - Houghteling, Harriot. Letters from Down North, 1922 (Box 66, Folder 1453)
    - Guide books and travel schedules, 1921, 1923, undated (Box 66, Folder 1452)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 66, Folder 1454)
    - Miscellaneous publications of The International Grenfell Association, 1924, undated (Box 66, Folder 1455)
    - Motorboat, 1924 October (Box 66, Folder 1456)
    - Newfoundland, undated (Box 66, Folder 1457)
    - Newfoundland Outport Nursing and Industrial Association, 1924-1926 (Box 66, Folder 1458)
    - Report of the Notre Dame Bay Memorial Hospital, 1926, 1928 (Box 66, Folder 1459)
    - Untitled publication, undated (Box 66, Folder 1460)
  - Radio script, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 1461)
  - Receipts, 1921-1922 (Box 66, Folder 1462)
  - Ship models, 1924-1926, undated (Box 66, Folder 1463-1464)
  - Ships' logs, 1922-1924 (Box 67, Folder 1465)
  - White Bay Fund, 1922-1927, undated (Box 67, Folder 1466)
  - White Bay Unit, 1922-1926, undated (Box 67, Folder 1467-1484)
  - Memorabilia, undated (Box 68, Folder 1485)
  - Note cards, 1922-1923,undated (Box 68, Folder 1486)
  - Note cards, undated (Box 69, Folder 1487)
  - Photographs: album, 1921-1925 (Box 70, Folder 1488)
  - Roll of ship model plans, undated (Box 70, Folder 1488)
- Organizations and Causes, 1916-1968; Series IV; 6.5' (16 boxes)
  ORGANIZATIONS AND CAUSES, Series IV, is divided into four subsections: American Friends Service Committee, Society of Friends, Japanese Relocation, and Other Causes. Correspondence comes first in American Friends Service Committee and is followed by papers that are arranged consistent with the organizational structure of the Service Committee. The material in the other three subsections is alphabetically arranged.
  - American Friends Service Committee
    - Correspondence, 1940-1968, undated (Box 71, Folder 1489-1511)
    - General, 1940-1968, undated (Box 71, Folder 1512-1513)
      - Annual reports, 1941-1942 (Box 71, Folder 1514)
      - Annual reports, 1943-1965 (Box 72, Folder 1515-1517)
      - Bulletins, 1940-1964 (Box 72, Folder 1518-1520)
      - Lists, undated (Box 72, Folder 1521)
      - Lists of overseas workers, 1917-1925 undated (Box 72, Folder 1522)
      - Minutes of meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 72, Folder 1523)
      - Newsletters, 1947-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1524-1528)
      - Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 72, Folder 1529)
      - Organization charts, 1940-1948, undated (Box 72, Folder 1530)
      - Overseas work, 1943-1956, undated (Box 72, Folder 1531-1532)
      - Pamphlets, 1939-1967, undated (Box 72, Folder 1533-1535)
      - Pamphlets on peace, 1940, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 1536)
      - Pamphlets on summer service, 1943, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 1537)
      - Staff meeting notes, 1947-1949 (Box 72, Folder 1538-1541)
      - Statement by Elizabeth Page Harris, undated (Box 72, Folder 1542)
    - Executive Board
      - Memoranda, 1948-1955 (Box 72, Folder 1543)
      - Minutes of meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 72, Folder 1544)
      - Minutes of meetings, 1952-1955 (Box 73, Folder 1545)
    - Regional Offices
      - Hidden Villa project, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 1546)
      - New England, 1955, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 1547)
      - Pacific Northwest, 1956, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 1548)
      - Southern California Branch
        - "Community Frontiers", 1941-1942 (Box 73, Folder 1549)
        - Minutes of meetings, 1941-1944 (Box 73, Folder 1550-1553)
        - Minutes of Executive Committee meetings, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 1554)
        - Minutes of Foreign Service Section meetings, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 1555)
        - Minutes of Refugee Committee meetings, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 1556)
        - Minutes of Social-Industrial Section meetings, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 1557)
        - "News Notes", 1942-1946 (Box 73, Folder 1558-1560)
        - Papers, 1942-1945, undated (Box 73, Folder 1561)
    - Civilian Public Service Section, 1942-1944
      See also: Box 83, folders 1809-1817
      - Committee meetings, 1942-1944 (Box 73, Folder 1562)
      - "News Notes" of Northern California Service Board for Conscientious Objectors, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 1563)
      - Papers, 1942, undated (Box 73, Folder 1564)
      - "The Sage O'Pinion", 1942 (Box 73, Folder 1565)
      - San Dimas Rattler, 1941-1944 (Box 73, Folder 1566-1571)
    - Foreign Service Section
      - Executive Committee
        - Agendas, 1939-1959 (Box 73, Folder 1572)
        - Budgets and reports, 1948-1956 (Box 73, Folder 1573)
        - Foreign Service Bulletin, 1944-1947 (Box 73, Folder 1574-1575)
        - Memoranda, 1947-1953 (Box 74, Folder 1576-1577)
        - Memoranda to regional offices, 1950-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1578)
        - Minutes, 1939-1955 (Box 74, Folder 1579-1585)
      - Area reports, 1947-1949 (Box 74, Folder 1586-1587)
        - Austria, 1947-1951 (Box 74, Folder 1588)
        - China, 1947-1950 (Box 74, Folder 1589)
        - Finland, 1947-1949 (Box 74, Folder 1590)
        - France, 1945-1951, undated (Box 74, Folder 1591-1592)
        - Germany, 1947-1952 (Box 74, Folder 1593)
        - Hungary, 1947-1949 (Box 74, Folder 1594)
        - India, 1947-1951, undated (Box 74, Folder 1595)
        - Italy, 1949-1953 (Box 74, Folder 1596)
        - Japan, 1947-1955 (Box 74, Folder 1597)
        - Korea, 1950-1954 (Box 74, Folder 1598)
        - Palestine, 1949, 1953, undated (Box 74, Folder 1599)
        - Poland, 1947-1948 (Box 74, Folder 1600)
        - African Subcommittee, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 1601)
        - Displaced Persons Subcommittee, 1948-1952 (Box 74, Folder 1602)
        - Eastern European Subcommittee, 1949 (Box 75, Folder 1603)
        - Individual Services Subcommittee, 1948-1949 (Box 75, Folder 1604)
        - Scandanavian Subcommittee, 1948-1949 (Box 75, Folder 1605)
      - Educational Materials for Children, 1948 (Box 75, Folder 1606)
      - International Centers Subcommittee
        - Business cards, undated (Box 75, Folder 1607)
        - Conferences, 1948-1959 (Box 75, Folder 1608-1609)
        - Expenses and notes, 1945-1946, undated (Box 75, Folder 1610)
        - Individual Centers, 1947-1953 (Box 75, Folder 1611)
        - International Student Program, 1947-1953, undated (Box 75, Folder 1612)
        - Letters: Alexander, Horace G., 1953 (Box 75, Folder 1613)
        - Letters: Bailey, Moses, 1952, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 1614)
        - Letters: Bainton, Roland, 1948 (Box 75, Folder 1615)
        - Letters: Bowles, Gilbert, 1947 (Box 75, Folder 1616)